ShinY
深影
《财富战争》前情提要
Previously on Billions.
本字幕由 ShinY 深影字幕组原创翻译制作
深影字幕组论坛地址http://shinybbs.vip
这公司 原为阿克塞控股公司
This company, formerly known as Axe Holding Company,
■
阿克塞资产管理 和阿克塞银行
Axe Asset Management, and Axe Bank,
现在归我的了
belongs to me now.
以前的老大是个冷血杀手
We used to work for a killer.
现在的老大希望了解咱们的"感觉"
Now we got a guy who wants to know how we feel.
ShinY
深影
你就告诉我你需要些什么来获取成功
Just tell me what you need to succeed here.
■
ShinY
深影
■
翻译：  AlliumFistulosum 碳树 鲜虾鱼板面 Meow Cinnamon
一个我能信任和合作的老板
A boss I can trust and work with.
■
说说这些大炮 我不是来找人干仗的
The artillery. I didn't come looking for a war.
■
校对：  留德竹林在     后期： 飒白恬
我需要这个工作
I need this place.
但你们也需要我
But you fuckers need me too.
听着 你们这群混蛋 我们换了新将军
Listen, you motherfuckers, we've got a new general.
你们最好赶紧加入
You better get in fucking step.
ShinY
深影
■
但我和我的前任不同
I'm unlike the man who came before me.
因为我不犯法
I do not break the law.
亿万富翁能做到体面地犯法
Billionaires break the laws of decency.
我需要作正确的决定 用正确的方式
I need you to get to the right decision and approach.
但如果你能不纠结于一直以来的做事方式呢
What if we weren't attached to the way it's always been done.
但我现在要创建一个普林斯名单
I am hereby creating The Prince List,
删掉目前投资的
which involves shedding all
ShinY
深影
所有不干净的资本
the dirty capital currently invested.
ShinY
深影
跟我来
Follow me!
好的
Yeah!
你想要战争 得偿所愿
You wanted your war, you got it.
准备发射
Fire in the hole.
财富战争 第六季第二集
美国摇滚乐队Stone Temple Pilots的歌曲
♪而我觉得♪
And I feel
♪是在虚度光阴 去吧♪
That time's a-wasting, go
♪你明天又要去往何方♪
So where ya going to Tomorrow?
♪而我明白♪
And I see
♪你又何必在意♪
So would you even care?
差点而已 很好
Almost. Good.
再来
Again.
在城市里生活久了 手生疏了 迈克
Hands go a little softer in the big city, Mike?
他会告诉你他在采石场工作
Oh, he'll tell ya he's a quarry man,
一个天生的石灰石工
a limestoner from birth, that he was...
从小一手老茧
Born with calluses.
也的确如此
Which is true.
但你也不能整天就数钱
But you can't keep 'em counting dollar bills.
只数大钱
Just get bigger ones.
钻石形状的
Diamond shaped.
你想试试另一条线路吗 迈克
You wanna try a different route, Mike?
不 我要搞定这个
No. I gotta send this.
就跟着她做
Just do what she did.
我不是安迪
I'm no Andy,
不然我就是教练了
or I'd be coaching the games.
洛杉矶 2028年 吊炸了
L.A. 2028. Badass.
一个美国人带领的美国队
An American coaching an American team
前往美国奥运会
for an American Olympics.
大有机会去创造历史
Lot of room to make history there.
和这次跳跃一样 迈克
Just like with this jump, Mike,
不要过分强调其重要性
you wanna downplay the significance.
看好落手点 然后带动自己往那去
See the handhold and will yourself to it.
来吧
Just do it.
更靠近一点
Closer.
你得在洛杉矶待多久
How long do you have to be in L.A. for?
看看这个多久能建好
We'll see how long it takes to build this thing.
这石群的施工下周开始
Construction on the complex starts next week.
我们再试一次吧 迈克
Let's try this again, Mike.
我明早就回去了
I'm heading back in the morning.
我觉得 下次你能在跳跃之前
I think if you can get your left hand in that crimp
左手先够到那石边 你就能完成了
before you go for the dyno, you'd have it.
要在我走之前吃个晚饭吗
Uh-huh. Wanna grab dinner before I leave?
我们不能那样子
We're not going to do that.
你可以冒充货运人
You can take the next months' shipment
跟着下个月的船运
in the name of a freight forwarder.
货运人
Freight forwarder?
货运人和报关人
Freight forwarder and a customs broker.
行了吧
All right?
很好 很好 所以你的下一步计划是什么
Good, good, good. Where are you going with this?
你听话就行
You just listen.
我们会轻松搞定的
We're gonna stand this thing on its head.
注意一下
Eyes up.
梅森碳能 你们也是
Mase Carb. You, too.
爱国人士 美国独立战争中提醒民众英军进犯
你知道现在人们怎么评价保罗·列维尔的吗
You know what some folks would call Paul Revere these days?
不切实际的
Dreamy?
一个告密者
A whistleblower.
他冒着生命危险 以自己的名誉
He called out bad actors at great risk to himself
换取了一场正义之战
and helped win a righteous war.
需要什么才能让人
What does it take to
打破阶级
break with the ranks
主动举报不法行为呢
and blow the whistle on wrongdoing?
大零售商一直都玩阴的
Big retailer's been playing dirty.
各种鞋子和装备上都写着"漂亮国制造"
Shoes and gears say "Made in China,"
但资本主义在压迫工人劳动
but they're using forced labor in Uighur concentration camps.
拉斯科运动服饰
Rask Sportswear.
拉斯科 我可喜欢了
Rask? Love them.
我碎人的时候都穿的它家沙滩裤
I wear their board shorts when I shred.
你什么时候
When you...?
在家 我玩太空狼人杀的时候
At home, when I play Among Us.
不过在我真要冲浪的时候
But if I did surf--
它家东西真不错
They do make great shit.
同感
All the same.
公司目前由创始人的儿子
Second-generation company currently headed up
小斯图尔特·拉斯科管理
by the founder's son, Stuart Rask, Jr.
在全球有超过一千家零售店
It has over 1,000 retail locations worldwide.
市场价值 三百亿美元
Market cap, 30 billion dollars.
而我们要做空它
And we're gonna short the snot out of it.
我想要像《奇爱博士》中斯利姆·佩金斯
I want us positioned to take this ride down
骑着核弹一样搞定这事
like Slim Pickens on the nuke in Strangelove.
一直空到底 然后...
All the way to the ground and then...
我肯定是反压榨的
I'm definitely anti-concentration camp,
但拉斯科多年来每个季度业绩都不错
but Rask hasn't had a bad quarter in literally years.
我不是夸张
And I'm not using literally figuratively,
真的是全都好
I'm using "literally" literally.
拉斯科有足够的财力
Rask has the financials
来抵御列宁格勒围城战
to withstand the siege of Leningrad.
是"羞辱和做空"
It's a "shame and short."
关键是建立超越数据的
The key is to build social pressure
舆论压力
that goes beyond the numbers.
让人无法接受穿着拉斯科
Make it unacceptable to be seen wearing Rask,
更别说持有他们的股票了
let alone holding their shares.
我去拿我的念珠
I'll grab my ma's rosary
来给我们祈祷
and pray while we're at it.
泰勒说的没错
Taylor sees it just right.
这家运动服饰是个完美目标
A sportswear brand is the perfect target.
我们一旦曝光拉斯科 他们赞助的运动员
Once we expose Rask, their sponsored athletes
会立刻撇清关系 粉丝也会随之跟上
will swear off the brand, the fans will follow.
股票也就完蛋了
The stock will be over.
要是我们真做到了 那能给普林斯名单上的
And if we pull it off, it will send a message
投资者 零售业和全世界
to the Prince List investors, the retail sector,
都发送信号了 对吧
and the world, won't it? Yeah.
这是表达态度的胜利
It's a statement win.
去做吧
Get after it.
为什么有阻力
Why were they pushing back?
他们担心自己是被当作
They're concerned they're being sent to charge
道德战用的机枪
a machinegun nest for moral reasons.
而他们也不相信会这么做的领导
And they don't trust a leader asking them to do that.
若是为了利润 贪婪
For profit, for greed,
他们会像诺曼底登陆一样冲锋
they'll charge like it's the beach at Normandy.
但不会是为了正义
But not for a cause.
科比一开始也不相信三角战术
Kobe was skeptical of the triangle at first.
像菲尔那样展示给他们 这样能取得胜利
Show 'em they can win under you like Phil did,
你便能和他们出生入死 但要达到目的...
you'll have 'em for life, but to do that, this...
必须得成功 明白了
Yeah. Has to work. Got it.
- 你知道你的任务吗 - 知道的
- You know your piece? - I do.
- 罗兹司法部长 - 你好
- AG Rhoades! - Hey.
温迪说过你会来接小孩
Wendy told me you'd be stopping by for your kids.
- 是的 - 我会
- Yes, sir. - I'll...
我会 就
I'll be, just,
如果你看到了一个五十五岁左右的女士
if you see a woman, mid-50s,
金发 穿着瑜伽服什么的...
blonde hair, yoga everything...
- 拖延她 - 啥...
- stall her. - What...
我马上回来 帮我看好门
I'll be right back. Guard the door.
行 让我帮你把孩子们带下来
Okay, let me get those kids down for you.
刚刚那是什么玩意儿
What the hell was that just now?
律师客户保密吗
Attorney-client?
可以
Sure.
十楼的某人把约会时间搞混了
Guy on the tenth floor got his dates mixed up.
需要些帮助来在他老婆回来前
Needed help getting his mistress out
把情人送出去
before the wife came back.
你可真是忠心耿耿
That is a tremendous feat of loyalty
又很会算时间 毫无疑问的
and timing, no doubt.
这里有你才能正常运转 对吧
You keep a lot of things straight around here, don't you?
- 我有我的高光时刻 - 不用太谦虚
- I have my moments. - Oh, come on.
这座楼里还有什么是
Is there anything in this building
不需要你的帮忙的吗
that works without your help?
雷斯勒夫人
Mrs. Resler!
你丈夫说好了让你到了就告知他
Your husband wanted me to buzz him the moment you arrived.
欢迎回来大城市
Welcome back to the big city.
现在我能在办公室看到你了吧
Can I expect you back at the office now, too?
办公室不是我开战的地方
Uh, the office is not where my new war is going to be waged.
至少一开始不是
Not at first.
拖拉机 又一次
Tractor, again?
或许吧
Maybe.
但比场地更重要的是传达的信息
But the venue matters less than the message,
是授权
the mandate.
我现在意识到不单单是一个亿万富翁
Now I realized it's not one billionaire
在这城里横行霸道
having his way with the city.
那确实不对 但还没有触及问题根本
That's wrong, but it's not existential.
而整个亿万富翁阶级对社会的影响呢
But the overall effect of the billionaire class?
他们就是个祸害
They're a scourge.
不行 我要在他们还活着的时候把他们搞死
No, I'm gonna get them where they live.
我明白了
I see.
我们要尽力搞定这事
We're gonna stand this thing on its head.
美国剧作家 语出《拜金一族》
你要学大卫·马梅么 行吧
Mamet? Okay.
他是在小镇里完成的
But he pulled that off in a small town.
- 这里是纽约 - 而纽约
- This is New York. - Well, New York
是很多个小镇组合了一起
is a lot of small towns stitched together.
欢迎 曼哈顿门卫及保管工会的各位
Welcome, members of Manhattan Door & Custodial.
作为工会的主席...
As president of this union...
我宣布本次会议开始
I call this meeting to order.
看啊
Look at this,
门卫的投票突然就被重视了
the doorman's vote must suddenly mean something,
现在州司法部长要来给我的小演讲砸场子了
because here's our state AG crashing my little speech.
下午好 各位 我并不是来砸场子的
Good afternoon, everyone. No. Far from crashing.
我是来这支持你们的
I am here to champion your cause.
我知道你们工作辛苦却无人珍惜
I know how hard you all work and how little thanks you get.
实际上 在最近的疫情期间
In fact, during the recent plague,
是谁站在了前线 看守着大门
who was on the front lines, manning the doors
而那些富得流油的住户却都躲起来了
while the well-heeled residents took cover?
你是说那些确实留在这里
You mean the ones who actually stuck around
没有跑去海边度假的吗
and didn't run off to their beach houses?
是的
I do. Yeah.
这里没有谁能像他们放几个月的长假
No one here got a months-long vacation like they did.
所以这就是为何 如果你们愿意
Which is why, if you'll have me,
我会去为你们争取危险津贴
I'm going to take up the fight to get you hazard back pay
来补偿你们疫情期间的工作
for the work you did during the pandemic.
我自愿成为你们的非官方代言人
I volunteer to be your unofficial mouthpiece
代替你们去和租户与物业管理委员会
and fight the Tenants and Property Management Board
作斗争
on your behalf.
不用都太激动的
Don't all cheer at once, please.
好了
Okay,
你是个游侠
you're a regular knight errant.
中世纪时 游侠寻求冒险来证明自己的骑士精神
而实际上 我们不需要你的帮助
Thing is, we don't want your help.
我们已经在与他们谈判
We're already in the middle of a negotiation with them,
取得了阶段性成果了
and we're making progress.
高知名度的官员的介入
Bringing in some high-profile state official
可能会引起委员会的不喜
could spook the TPMB
破坏之后的商谈
and ruin the forward movement.
再说 你也有自己的小九九
Plus, you got an angle.
我不知道是什么 但你肯定别有用心
I don't know what it is, but you do.
你需要知道吗
You need to know?
反正是于你有益的
As long as it serves you and yours?
你们这类人我们见多了 几乎每天都有
We see folks like you all day, every day.
嘴上应承得冠冕堂皇 背地不知搞什么勾当
We see what they say versus what they do.
我们凭什么相信你们会施以援手
Why should we believe you're going to help us?
我们根本就不了解你
We don't fucking know you.
我了解他
I know him.
他人品不差
He's all right.
多谢 拉法
Thank you, Rafa.
你读过新闻了对吧
You see the news, don't you?
我已经表达得相当明确了
I have made it quite plain that,
通过观察这个州 这个城市
in looking out upon this state and city,
我锁定了让它步入颓势的那一组罪魁祸首
I have identified the one group that has made them worse.
现在正是这些人想从你们身上汲利
And those are the very people trying to do you dirty now.
我和他们不一样
I am not like them.
就像拉法说的 我人品不差
Like Rafa said, I'm all right.
他认识我所有的家庭成员
And he knows my whole family.
我的妻儿
Wife and kids.
前妻
Ex-wife.
他前妻出手慷慨 会给丰厚的小费
Ex-wife is a generous tipper.
他的孩子乖巧礼貌 会说"请您"和"谢谢"
And his kids are "please" and "thank you."
很高兴听你这么说
Well, that's good to hear.
我的孩子们懂得示以尊重
And the reason my children show respect is
是因为他们知道
they know how I feel
我是如何看待那些为了群体的利益
about those who put themselves out there
挺身而出 奉献自己的人
for the greater good.
但你们知道你们这类人的问题在哪吗
But you know what the one problem with folks like you is?
你们忙于照顾他人
You're so busy taking care of others,
保护他们幸福的生活不遇见任何阻碍
of making sure that nothing gets in the way
你们将他人利益置于自己之前
of them living their best lives, that you put yourselves second.
甘然接受他们所愿意施予的
You just accept what's offered.
这种不公将于今日终结
That ends today!
现在终结
Now!
因为我知道该如何讨回应得的份
Because I know how to ask for what's deserved.
讨回血汗 讨回尊严
Earned. For dignity.
讨回尊重 这话不是代我自己说
Respect. And I'm going to use that not on my behalf.
是代你们说
But on yours.
你们觉得呢
What say you?!
一点也没错
Hell, yeah!
好吧 罗兹
All right, Rhoades.
去搞定他们吧
Go get 'em.
维克多说得对
Victor was right.
他一向是正确的
He's often right.
我长大的经历...
I grew up...
一直以为那样的人不存在了
Guys like that, I always assumed they were...
不 大多数情况下你想得没错
No, you'd be correct most of the time.
他只是个特例
And he's some of those things.
头脑还聪明
But he's smart.
让人赞叹啊
Fascinating.
不管何如 就运动品牌而言
Anyhoozit, when it comes to sports brands,
市场对原因的记忆转瞬即逝
the market has a short memory for causes,
却能把数字铭刻在史
a long one for numbers.
普林斯应该是知道的
Prince would know that.
市场那套他早就了然于心了
He'd have that knowledge baked in.
我找到了五个比拉斯科规模更小
I've found five less-established brands
但背后更脏的品牌
that're dirtier than Rask.
我预计 由于受拉斯科的影响
I expect similar brands like that will fall a little,
类似品牌的股价会降一阵子
in sympathy with Rask,
但情况会有多糟呢
but how much worse can it get?
远比你能想象的糟
Much worse.
这是我找到的所有问题 简直是日暮途穷
All sorts of egregious shit I'd spell out,
简直说不出口
except I hate spelling things out loud.
这感觉就跟明知自己正确
Almost as much as I hate being right
却无从证明一样的乏力讨厌
and not being able to prove it.
那就是金钱的意义 能作证据
That's what the money is, proof.
我们把整个板块蚕食干净吧
Let's mukbang the whole sector.
不 还是暂缓
No. Hold off for now.
阿克塞领导时 这或许大能奏效
This initiative would have worked under Axe,
但普林斯却有不同的权衡和优先考虑
but Prince has different priorities.
他追求的似乎不仅仅是利润
He seems to be after more than profits here.
所以呢 你是想说"他是个善良 聪明的人
So what, are you saying, "He's a kind man,
他有他的计划 有深思熟虑"吗
a wise man, he has plans, he has wisdom?"
因为那会使城市天翻地覆
'Cause vom city at that.
这我说不准 但我知道他不是阿克塞
I don't know yet, but I know he's not Axe.
我们运作的方式已非往日了
We're operating differently now.
梅森碳能公司也不是我们
Mase Carb's not going to be
唯一面临的阻力了
the siloed resistance anymore.
所以我们要信任这人吗
So we're gonna trust this guy?
我们静观其变 暂时妥协
We're throwing in. For now.
直到获得更多信息
Until we have more information.
坚守岗位
Stay on mission.
罗兹司法部长
Attorney General Rhoades,
我完全不懂你为什么要主动介入
I'm at a total loss as to why you've involved yourself in
租户及物业管理委员会
negotiations between our Tenants and Property Management Board
与门卫及保管工会 两方间的协商谈判
and the Doormen's and Custodial Union.
所有涉及本州成员的事务
All matters involving members of this state
都在我的职权范围内
are within my purview,
自然也包括你们两个优秀组织间的谈判
and that includes both your fine organizations.
尤其这次谈判还事关那些
But especially when it concerns those who are often
经常被权贵践踏的人的切身利益
trod upon by the powerful and wealthy.
所以我来帮他们辩护
So I have lent them my voice
并将我的办公室用作谈判场地
and my office as venue.
好吧 虽然他们根本不需要
Well, much as they don't need it,
- 我觉着不用 - 不需要吗
- I guess it's fine. - They don't?
对 我计划增加百分之二的管理费
No. I was already prepared to offer a two-percent increase
这是他们值得的
in management fees. They've earned it.
百分之二 很好的提议...
Two percent, that'd be great...
杜里奥 等等
Uh, Duilio, please.
请允许我先发言
Allow me.
百分之二跟小偷行径也没差了
Two percent is theft.
你不如直接抢劫 扒了他们的口袋
Might as well pick their fucking pockets.
那些可是在保护你安然熟睡的勇敢灵魂啊
These are the brave souls who protect you in your slumber.
如果董事会不同意增加百分之五
If this board won't agree to five percent,
那么这场谈判的本质就是一场剥削做戏
then these negotiations are nothing but a cruel charade.
恕我们无法接受
No dice.
就因为他说的吗 他是巴西尼吗
Because he said? He's Barzini?
《教父》中柯里昂家族的主要对手 第二大黑手党领袖
拉扎拉先生...
Well, Mr. Lazarra...
嗯 我知道巴德·拉扎拉是谁
Yeah, I know who Bud Lazarra is
也知道他在这城市坐拥多少财富
and how much real estate he owns in this city.
但你也许不知道 我们代表了这里的居民
What you might not know is, I speak for the residents.
我们不会付钱的
And we're not paying.
你的脸是晒伤 冻伤还是酒精喝成的
Sunburn, windburn, or whiskey?
三者结合
It's all three.
冲浪 跑马 还有格兰威特威士忌
Surf, turf, and Glenlivet.
我们中大多数人都因新冠而逃离了城市
Most of us skipped town for Covid.
浅举几例 汉普顿 韦尔 加勒比地区
Here the Hamptons, Vail, Caribbean.
他们甚至允许资产最为富有的人
They even let some especially high-net-worth
进入新西兰
individuals into New Zealand.
因此 门卫的工作量简直降到了最轻
So the doormen had the easiest workday they've ever seen.
先生 这就是问题所在啊
Ah, sir, this is the problem exactly.
像你们这样富得流油的居民
Wealthy residents like yourselves
安安全全地去了度假别墅避难
retreated to the comfort of their many vacation homes,
把他们的助手抛在身后
leaving their helpers behind,
继续守卫他们空荡荡的公寓楼
guarding their empty apartments,
将性命赤裸裸地暴露在
fully exposed at the very epicenter of a pandemic
这当代前所未有的流行病爆发的中心
unparalleled in modern history.
你欠他们太多了
You stand in their debt.
我感到奇怪的是 我们尽忠职守的门卫
I find it curious that our doormen
并没有亲自对我们提及这些需求
hadn't thought to bring this up themselves.
只有你 打着他们的旗号高谈阔论
And then you show up, flinging your shit all around
如同动物园的大猩猩耀武扬威
like a chimpanzee at the zoo.
我早就听说过你的精彩演讲 罗兹
I've heard about your theatrics, Rhoades.
但可惜 你在这里不会收获任何掌声
But you'll receive no applause here
因为我有更重要的事情要处理
'cause I've got better things to do.
就这样吗
That's it?
拉扎拉先生走了 会议就结束了
The meeting's done when Lazarra is.
那是不对的 这不对
That was wrong. This is wrong.
对啊 他们凭什么那样瞧不起你们
Yeah. I mean how can they shortside you like that?
- 百分之二打发叫花子吗 - 不是他们 是你
- I mean, two percent? - Not them. You.
他们给的提案已经能让大家满意了
They agreed to a bump that would make my guys glad,
但现在我们屁都没争取到
but now we're getting zilch.
那你是让我袖手旁观
You would have me sit back
看你们被捉弄咯
and let them take us for a ride, then?
满足于远低于你们应得的补偿吗
Settle for less than your union deserves?
- 不可能 - 那你有什么好建议
- No way. - What do you propose?
我认为你的人可以开始罢工抗议了
I think it's time for your boys to go on strike.
不可能 我不能逼他们离开
Uh-huh. No way. I can't make them go out.
尤其他们还摆出了一个不错的条件
Not when there's a real offer on the table.
我...
I...
听着 先生
Look, man.
我是来帮忙的
I'm here to help.
我是带着那根该死的胡萝卜来的 知道吗
I led with the goddamn carrot, you know?
即"胡萝卜和大棒" 一种奖励与惩罚并存的激励政策
我们得戮力同心 朝一个方向前进
Let's just keep going in that direction, together.
那你得给我看看那根大棒啊
You're gonna have to show me the stick.
大棒
Ah, the stick.
那就是其他机构的职责了
Well, that is wielded by other agencies.
你知道财税部吗
The DTF, you know?
州税务和财政部门
The state Department of Taxation and Finance.
专查你和你手下所享受的那些
All that unreported income from holiday tips
未申报的度假小费收入
you and your boys enjoy.
我会试着阻拦他们 但总有一天
I'll try to fight 'em off, but at some point,
我不得不调查你们
I'll have to investigate
甚至其他每一个服务工会
and widen the scope to every other service union,
让他们知道 一切起源于门卫
letting them know that the pattern started with the doormen.
这对你的社交生活一定大有裨益
Which should do wonders for your social lives.
你真行
Jesus.
是啊 没错
Yeah. Well.
就像我说的
Like I said,
我会试着拦住他们
I'll try to fight 'em off,
不过既然你问到了大棒 我就告诉你
but you were asking about the stick, and that's it.
其威力之大 能粉碎你的头骨呢
The one that's going to crack you across the skull.
所以...
So...
所以
So,
我想我们会罢工的
I guess we're on strike.
利婉算了下数据
Rian ran the numbers.
存在更有利可图的方式 能在同一领域
There are more profitable ways to make the same point
达成同样的目的
in the same sector.
你认为普林斯缺乏公开市场经验的弱点
You think Prince's lack of experience
正在慢慢显现出来吗
in the public markets is showing?
不 意不在此
No, it's not that.
他有足够的智慧和精准的直觉 配得上这里
He has the brainpower and the right instincts for this place.
那你为何不直接找他谈谈
Then why don't you just talk to him,
表达你所持见解 以数据辅证
voice your reservations, show him your data?
我在想 这可能是个考验
I'm considering that this might all be a test.
他更希望我们与他对峙 针锋相对
Does he want us to confront him,
还是希望我们对他抱有完全的信任
or does he want us to show that we trust him?
考验
A test?
听起来像阿克塞耍的手段 而非普林斯所为
That sounds like an Axe move, not something Prince would do.
- 我认为不是考验 - 你认为他被误导了
- I say there's no test. - So you think he's misguided?
我不能为你下结论
I'm not going to make that kind of an assessment for you.
如果你心存疑虑 直接找普林斯谈谈吧
If you have your doubts, talk to Prince.
如果我要去质问这里每一个
If I confronted every person here who gave me reason
不时引起我怀疑的人
to doubt them from time to time,
可能每一场我都得戴上头盔和话筒才行
I'd need headgear and mouthpiece for every single conversation.
- 每个人 - 对
- Everyone? - Yes.
就目前的公司状况 每个人都无法排除
Present company not excluded.
亚历克斯说他马上就会发帖子了
Alex said he'd be posting right about now.
我查查抖音
Let's check the Tok.
每次我想打开抖音
Every time I try to open it,
都会被大嚷大叫的戈登·拉姆齐攫取眼球
I'm accosted by Gordon Ramsay yelling at someone.
顶级厨神 因在烹饪节目的暴躁严格的性格出名
嗨 大家好 我是亚历克斯
Hey, everyone, this is Alex.
我想分享我对拉斯科运动器械公司的看法
I wanted to let you guys know how I feel about Rask gear.
我刚刚发现 他们剥削廉价劳动力
I just found out they've been using unethical labor
一直以来都在掩饰真相 所以我选择使用
and lying about it for years, which is why I use
乐斯菲斯的运动产品 那是我信赖的品牌
the NorthFace, a company I can trust.
美国著名户外运动品牌
拉斯科简直是品牌界的"垃圾箱大火"
Rask is a Dumpster fire of a company,
隐喻灾难性的恶劣情况
烧了才对
so this feels about right.
已经有几十万观看了
Hundreds of thousands of views already.
用户们都进行合拍点评
People doing stitches and duets.
扩散到推特上了
It's made it to Twitter.
大阪直美也将放弃赞助
Naomi Osaka is dropping their sponsorship, too.
女足也在说抵制
Women's soccer's talking a boycott.
股价在下跌
Stock price is falling.
好极了
Excellent.
我看到门卫正式罢工了
I saw that the doormen are officially on strike.
曼哈顿最豪华的
Hmm, the foyers of Manhattan's
大楼门厅里没人了
wealthiest buildings stand empty.
好的
Good.
租户和物业管理委员会
The, uh, negotiation meeting
谈判会议
with the Tenants and Property Management Board
是按你的预期进展的吗
went the way you thought it would?
我拒绝了他们的无谓的妥协
I rejected their paltry attempts at compromise
惹怒了他们 卡尔
and worked them all up into a rage. Karl!
把这些直接送到他们手上
Take these and deliver them directly.
地址在这
Addresses are on there.
我想让你直接把他们送到收件人手上
I want them to go straight from your hand to their recipient's.
不经过转手
No middlemen.
这将是一次不错的中央公园之旅
This will be a real tour of Central Park views.
不过乘飞艇会更好一点
Only better way is by blimp.
这一份我亲自送
This one I will deliver myself.
巴德·拉扎拉 他是关键
Bud Lazarra. He's the key.
其他居民都看他眼色行事
The other residents will take their cues from him.
我的天呐
Christ on a bike!
集中注意力 巴德
Okay, Bud, keep your focus.
这很有趣
You know what? It's funny,
我听说 "不要动你的头" 是假的
I'd heard that whole "don't move your head" thing was a myth.
但就在你挥杆前
But right before you shanked it, Buddy-boy,
我确实发现了颅骨区域的一些晃动
I did detect some wobble in the cranial area.
不过我确信布里德先生能够指导您改正
But I'm sure Mr. Breed here can train that out of you.
如果你不是法庭的官员
If you weren't an officer of the court,
你自己的颅骨区域会震动的 罗兹
your own cranial area would be getting quite a jolt, Rhoades.
你现在想打我吗
Think you wanna hit me now?
这是给你的
This is for you.
门卫危险津贴的账单
A bill for the doormen's hazard pay.
如果你荒唐的行为不是那么令人讨厌的话
I might find your antics amusing
我其实会觉得很可笑
if they weren't such a nuisance.
这就像在万圣节前夜装饰你的房子
It's like getting your house egged on All Hallow's Eve.
但是你的设想不会实现的罗兹
But your scheme won't work, Rhoades.
这话他听过很多了
He gets that a lot.
从比你更有权力的人那里
Hmm. And from men even more entitled than yourself.
而这真的有效
Hmm. And they do work, so...
所以你该再考虑一下
you might want to think about that.
好的
Yeah.
我们希望能及时付款
And we expect timely payment.
很高兴见到布里斯特
Nice to meetcha, Breedster.
他能用上你鼓励性的指导
He can use every bit of that encouraging coaching of yours.
好的 我们继续
All right, Bud, let's do this.
你还会遇到更分散你注意力的事
You're going to face bigger distractions than that.
大学联盟发了推特 她抨击了拉斯科
AOC just tweeted. She blasted Rask.
这是个重量级选手
Now there's a heavy hitter.
有形成趋势吗 市场有反应吗
Is it trending? Has the market reacted?
是的 以及 是的
Yes and yes.
降到十七美金每股了
We're down to $17.00 a share.
你好像没有感到很惊讶
You didn't seem quite surprised enough.
我没有吗
Wasn't I?
那条推特不会仅仅是靠运气
That tweet can't just be good luck.
好的 我打过电话了
All right. I made a call.
没什么不恰当的语言
Nothing improper.
只是确保她的员工都知道这个问题了
Made sure her staffers knew the issue.
很好 其他的怎么样
Nicely done. What about the other thing?
租用的设备要运去宾夕法尼亚州
The rentable equipment is being pulled to Pennsylvania,
在候机楼候机
to wait in the wings.
公司怎么样了
What about the companies that own?
他们与其他地方的项目有关
They're tied up with projects elsewhere.
行业的供应链很薄弱
Supply chain is thin in the industry right now,
关键转折点
a real flexion point.
我知道这利害关系 也知道该如何做
I know the stakes here. And I knew what to do.
但如果需要我再去检查...
But if it brings reassurance to check that I've--
足够了
Fair enough.
谢谢
And thank you.
你在这就方便了
It's convenient that you're up here.
我有个人力资源的问题
I have an HR matter.
- 好的 有什么我能帮忙的 - 我要开除利婉
- Sure. How can I help? - I'm going to fire Rian.
哇
Whoa.
好的 原因呢
Okay. Reason?
她直接违背了我的指令
She directly disobeyed my orders.
没有商榷的空间吗
No room for ambiguity?
没有 她做了我不让她做的事
None. She took a position I told her not to take.
实际上 有好几次
Several, actually.
不仅鲁莽而且危险
Not only is it reckless, but it's also dangerous.
- 做的聪明吗 - 有什么关系吗
- Was it smart? - Does that matter?
跟我来
Come with me.
开掉利婉可能是你作为老板的最好决定
Firing Rian may be the best move for you as a boss,
但是从做人的角度来说并不好
but it's not the best move for you as a person,
整体来说
holistically.
我们什么时候开始考虑总体了
Since when do we do holistically in this place?
新的地方 新的事情
New place, new thing.
而且在这里适用 因为
And it applies, since the whole reason
你要开除她的主要原因是她伤害了你的感情
you want to fire her is she hurt your feelings.
如果上校下达命令
If a colonel gives an order--
这不是《红一纵队》
This is not The Big Red One.
美国战争片 士官长和四位士兵 在枪林弹雨中勇往直前
是你想从你的助手那得到盲目的信任
This is about you wanting blind trust from your acolyte.
这是文化契合
It's about culture fit.
我们换了新的环境
We've undergone a sea change here,
但利婉仍在按旧规则行事
and Rian's still playing by the old rules.
她已经证明自己无法或不愿适应
She's proven herself unable or unwilling to adapt.
你适应了吗 泰勒
And have you adjusted, Taylor?
真的吗
Really?
因为开除利婉听起来就像
Because firing Rian sounds like exactly
阿克塞站在你的立场会做的事
what Axe would do if he were in your shoes.
目标是十五美元 尽力接近
Aim for 15, as close as you can get.
让我们狠狠的压价
Let's whack those fucking bids like they're
就像弗兰克·潘坦利居要去作证一样
Frankie Pentangeli about to testify!
《教父》中人物
你确定我们还能听他的指挥吗
Are you sure we can still take directions from him?
他还是
He's still the...
无论他的工作头衔是什么
whatever his job title is.
准备好 差不多
Ready now, almost there.
为什么都挤在一起
Why are we huddling up?
都在买入
Play's already been called.
就先准备好一旦股票到十五美金
Just readying the team to cover their positions
大家就补进
as soon as the stock hits $15.
盈得可观的利润
For a nice tidy profit.
我买阿克塞资本不是要盈可观利
I didn't buy Axe Cap for tidy.
我想要大的暴利
I want a big, sloppy profit.
用你的话说 瓦格斯 一头怪兽猪 猪斯拉
In your words, Wags, "A monster pig. A Hogzilla."
都等到跌到五以下
Everyone, hold till the stock dips under five.
就是我了 球手
Five it is, baller.
这不是有问题吗
Isn't that going to be a problem?
关于做空有个问题
There's a problem with the short.
你也
You too?
很高兴你在这泰勒
I'm glad you're here, Taylor.
你也该知道
You should both know.
我要说两件事
I have two things to disclose.
一个是 我和斯图伊·拉斯科是老朋友
One. I'm old pals with Stuey Rask.
我和斯图伊在摇滚幻想营认识的
Stuey and I met at rock fantasy camp.
老鹰乐队《Lyin' Eyes》
♪你无法隐藏♪
You can't hide
♪你说谎的眼神♪
Your lyin' eyes
♪你的微笑♪
And your smile
♪是一种伪装♪
Is a thin disguise
♪我以为♪
I thought by now
♪你现在会明白♪
You'd realize
♪你无法掩饰♪
There ain't no way to hide
♪你说谎的眼神♪
Your lyin' eyes
其他大多数参与者都是郊区的爸爸
Most of the other attendees were suburban dads
认为四瓶精酿 一支大麻烟 再上上P站
who thought four IPAs, a joint, and a spin on Pornhub
就是疯狂的一晚了
was a wild night.
我和斯图伊
Stuey and I...
惺惺相惜
understood each other.
我们志同道合
We were kindred spirits,
不同世界的摇滚之神
rock gods from another life.
他还让我唱格列弗雷的部分
He even lets me sing the Glenn Frey parts.
很感人
Touching.
你说了 有两件事
But you said you had two things.
那另外一件要说的是什么
What else do you need to disclose?
那只股票即将反弹
That stock is about to rebound.
非常快
Very soon.
- 怎么会 - 你做了什么
- How? - What'd you do?
我谈成了一项收购协议
I negotiated a buyout,
这样普林斯就能从做空中获利
so that Prince could profit off the short.
但后来我加了一部分 这样斯图伊不会有事
But then I added a part two so that Stuey would be okay.
走
Come on.
看 我安排了一个买家
See, I put a buyer in place.
他接管的消息一传出
As soon as word of the takeover gets out,
拉斯科的股票就会回升
the Rask stock's gonna pop.
你毁了我的计划
You ruined my play
让数亿美元的资本面临风险
and put hundreds of millions in capital at risk
就因为你想唱老鹰乐队的歌
because you wanted to sing Eagles songs.
他让我唱格列弗雷的部分
He lets me sing the Glenn Frey parts.
我不关心
I don't care!
他是想这样你们可以双赢
He thought you could both win this way.
你吃到了空头的收益
You'd profit off the short,
拉斯科可以恢复
and Rask would still recover.
如果拉斯科 恢复了 我就赢不了了
If Rask recovers, I don't win.
布隆伯格的警报解除了
Uh-oh. The Bloomberg alert just dropped.
"阿斯特拉运动准备收购拉斯科运动服饰
"Astra Sports is preparing an offer to buy Rask Sportswear,
并令小斯图尔特·拉斯科继续
leaving Stuart Rask, Jr.,
担任首席执行官十年
in as CEO for ten years."
股票已经在反弹了
Stock is already rebounding.
我们的钱就要大出血了
We're hemorrhaging money by the second.
我们要试着补进
We could try and cover our position.
我们要阻止这次收购
We have to stop this takeover from happening.
这是唯一的方式
It's the only way.
在罗宾汉大侠们跳出来斥责他
Before the Robinhood knuckleheads jump on him
或者我们被零售浪潮冲走之前
or we're washed away by the retail wave.
你造成的麻烦 自己解决
You created this problem, fix it.
- 我要怎么解决 - 如果我问你这个问题
- How can I fix it? - If I asked you that question,
你会说我是个足智多谋的混蛋
you'd say I'm a resourceful motherfucker.
我可以 我是
I can be. I am.
你也会说 如果拉斯科藏了什么东西
You might also say, "If there's something Rask is hiding,
我会查出来 事实上 我已经查出来了
I'll Easy Rawlins that shit. In fact, I have it already."
我可能
I might. Yeah.
但是要用这种肮脏的手段对付斯图伊
But to do Stu dirty like that...
格列·弗雷永远不会对唐亨利做这样的事
I mean, Glenn would never have done that to Don Henley.
同为老鹰乐队成员
拉斯科不是亨利
Rask isn't Henley.
网球运动员
他是费德勒
He's Felder.
别让我做出他们对他做的那种事
Don't make me do to you what they did to him.
像因为某些原因解雇我
Would it be along the lines of firing me for cause,
让我卷入诉讼
tying me up in lawsuits
强制执行竞业禁止等等
to enforce a non-compete, et cetera?
你说队伍的成员 瓦格斯 就做队员
You say you're on the team, Wags. Be on the team.
做好一个队员应该做的事
Do the thing the team guy does,
不然就离开 你想怎么样
or you're not on the team, are you?
你现在在你脑袋在想些什么
What cockamamie scheme do you have cooking in that
可笑的方案 儿子
Crock-Pot of a head of yours now, Sonny?
这是我和亿万富翁这一犯罪阶级
It is the first battle in the new war I'm waging,
之间进行的第一次较量
against the billionaires, the criminal class.
我要从门卫开始
And I'm starting with the doormen.
你什么时候开始成为强尼午餐桶的代言人了
Since when are you the voice of Johnnie Lunch Bucket?
因为它符合我的选民的需要
Since it suits the needs of my constituents.
从短期和长期来看
In the short and long term.
我在听
I'm listening.
但我不再说了
But I'm not saying any more.
我将保留我自己的建议
I'm going to keep my own counsel.
我的门卫非常高兴
Ah, hell. My doorman is perfectly happy.
他向我打招呼的时候总是微笑
He always has a big smile
爸爸 那是他的工作
That is his job, Dad.
等我拿下了巴德·拉扎拉
And you will have to pay the bill,
你也要付账单
just as soon as Bud Lazarra cracks.
那是不可能的
That'll never happen.
你不会想招惹拉扎拉的
You'd do not want to mess with Lazarra.
为什么 难道你已经站他那边了
Why, because you've thrown in with him already?
不 我不会再和你的敌人联手了
Nah, I'm done teaming up with your enemies.
我上次就站错队了
I took the wrong side of that bet for the last time.
这对我来说可是个好消息
Well, I'm glad to hear it.
儿子 你还记得
Son, do you remember
我们在葡萄园房子里
the first summer
度过的第一个夏天吗
that we took the house at the Vineyard?
你也就五六岁吧
You were probably five or six.
记得
Mm-hmm, I do.
你想再去那度个假吗
Are you contemplating an extended vacation?
或许我应该去 但是不
Perhaps I should be, but no.
你当时水性可不怎么好
You were a feeble swimmer, at best.
终于有一天
Finally, one day,
你游出了海岸
you got out past the shore break
游到了一块比较平静的海域
to the calmer water.
然后转过头对着我
You turned to show me,
脸上挂着大大的骄傲的微笑
big, proud smile on your face.
甚至没注意到朝你扑过去的海浪
You didn't see the wave coming.
- 那你没有提醒我 - 提醒你
- And you didn't warn me? - Warn you?!
为了吸引你的注意力 我还鼓了掌
I clapped and kept your attention on me
直到海浪扑过来吞没了你
until the wave came and wiped you out completely.
因为我知道 吃点苦头 你才能明白这一课
I knew it was a lesson you needed to learn the hard way.
我两只耳朵都感染了
I got infections in both ears.
那你现在知道了
So, now you oughta know,
永远不要背对海洋般的力量
don't turn your back on oceanic forces.
我现在不想给你上课了
See, I'm done teaching you lessons.
现在 我在专心教育你妹妹
Those are for your sister now.
但这一次海浪扑过来之前
I am warnin' you this time,
我就提醒提醒你
before the wave breaks.
拉扎拉是很强的对手
Lazarra's formidable.
感谢您的提醒
I appreciate the warning
感谢您的好心
as a gesture of goodwill.
也是我们之间新关系开始的标志
And a mark of the beginning of a new phase of our relationship.
但你我都心知肚明
But you and I both know
当我遇到一只庞大的猎物时
when I get big game in my sights...
我绝不会轻易放下猎枪
I can't lower my rifle.
儿子 既然这样的话
Well, in that case, my boy,
祝你好运
I wish you luck.
我会裹好荧光橙外衣
I'll don my blaze orange...
避开你们的交战区
and step out of the line of fire.
晚安 爸爸
Goodnight, Dad.
不好意思
Excuse me!
嗨 我是安迪·萨尔特
Hi. I'm Andy Salter.
如果你还有问题的话 我冠姓普林斯
There's Prince tacked on there, if you're being particular.
我明白了 你是他前妻 还是
Of course! You're his ex-wife, or--
抱歉 还没离吗...
Sorry, are you still...
一切都好 我就知道我们很快就会见面
Hi. Good. I figured it wouldn't be too long.
从上次见到你之后
Since the last time I saw you,
我的攀岩队的主要赞助商
the main sponsor of my climbing team
甚至整个项目都有可能破产
and the entire games is potentially bankrupt.
而且我刚刚得知
And I just learned that the construction company
为我建造培训设施的建筑公司
that's building my training facility
都拿不到那些需要的设施了
can't get the equipment they need.
那些重型机器都被运走了
Somehow the heavy machinery got diverted.
而现在 洛杉矶的东道主地位也岌岌可危
And now, L.A.'s host status is on life support.
已经在开会讨论取消资格
Meetings are being held about pulling it.
委员会都开始准备重新竞标了
The commission's set to start re-shopping the bid.
- 一切都在计划中 - 行
- There's a plan. - Yeah.
很明显
That's clear.
一切都会顺利解决的
It's all going to be resolved.
你为什么要毁了我的梦想
Why are you cratering my dream gig?
你还记得我们的第三次约会吗
Do you remember our third date?
印第安纳州博览会那次
The Indiana State Fair?
每个摊位上 我们都要争个高低
We turned every booth into a competition.
如果套圈和气球飞镖有世界纪录的话
I swear, if they kept records for the milk bottle ring toss
我们肯定能创造奇迹
and the balloon dart, we would have smashed them.
我走的时候带着一大堆毛绒玩具
I had armloads of those shitty stuffed animals.
在我人生中能被称为顿悟的时刻
A few times in my life, I've had,
也只有那么几次
I guess folks would call them epiphanies.
有些东西在一瞬间变得清晰起来
Where something just came clear, in an instant.
每一次都为其他事赋予了意义
And each one set the tone for everything else.
一次是我第一次摸到篮球
One was when I first picked up a basketball.
一次是我意识到我能在一瞬间
The other was when I realized that I was able to understand
发现一个机会的潜在价值
the intrinsic value of an opportunity in an instant,
还有一次 就是博览会的那天晚上
and then there was that night at the fair.
我知道你就是那个人
I knew you were the one.
事实证明这三次顿悟我都没看走眼
I was right about all three.
没错
Yeah.
我一直都相信你
No doubt.
但是篮球和市场
But basketball and markets
都没有经纪人或是自己的想法
don't have agencies or free will of their own.
但我有
I do.
我看到你看向我的眼神了
I see the way you look at me.
一直
Still.
爱你
Loving you.
欣赏你
Admiring you.
为你着迷
Still being attracted to you.
但这并不代表着我们想过一样的生活
None of that means we want to live the same kind of life.
这也不意味着你可以擅自
And none of that means you get to unilaterally decide
- 替我做决定 - 我可没有这么做
- the direction of mine. - I've never done that.
你现在就在这么做
You're trying to do that now.
我这是为了进行整个无良行业中
This is about cleaning up a dirty company
无良公司的清理
and an entire industry along with it.
- 这不止是你我间的事 - 对对对
- It's bigger than us. - Yeah. Sure it is.
没错 我是能从中获利
Fine, yes, I stand to profit.
收益还不菲
Hugely, in fact.
如果拉斯科倒台了 我能赚十倍
It's a ten-bagger if Rask blows up.
我不是这个意思
That's not what I meant.
你来搞我的赞助商不是一个巧合
It's no coincidence that you got involved with my sponsor.
你有数不尽的方法赚上一笔
There are plenty of other ways to make a point and a profit.
好吧 我当初调查这家公司是为了你
Okay. I looked into the company because of your proximity to it,
接着就看到了这个我决不能放弃的机会
and I saw an opportunity that was too important to pass up.
- 迈克 - 我有办法让我们双赢的
- Mike... - I have a way we can both win.
我本来已经赢了
I was already winning.
我只是想过自己的生活
I'm just trying to do my own thing,
是你不肯放过我
and you can't leave it alone.
你跟我说实话 你是不是想用钱
Be honest with me-- are you trying to buy back
- 挽回我们的关系 - 我从没放弃过
- the relationship you want? - I haven't given up.
那你该放弃了
You should, though.
现在你只需要相信我
I just need you to trust me
然后静待事件发展就好了
and see how this is going to resolve.
如果你说的是真的 是我一直强求你留下
If what you say is true, that I'm not letting you go,
那你应该知道
then you have to also know
我早就料到你会来找我了
I anticipated your reaction to it.
当你在攀岩的时候
When you're on the mountain,
你能分清什么是你应该做的
you can know what you're supposed to do,
又有什么是你想做的
what you're trying to do.
这并不意味着你能做成所有事
It doesn't mean you can pull it off.
一旦你失败了
And if you try and fail,
你可能没机会再来一次了
there may not be a path to recover.
所以你现在要搞一些大动作
So if you are making some big move here,
最好已经有了下脚点
be really sure you have your footing.
因为你我现在被绑在一条绳子上
Because you and I are tied to the same rope now,
你要是失手了 也会把我拉下去
and if you peel off, you take me down with you.
罢工被取消了
Strike's been called off.
门卫们现在穿上制服 回到岗位上了
Doormen are back in uniform and back at their posts.
那些亿万富翁们还没给钱吗
Billionaires still haven't paid?
没呢
Nope.
他们的动作倒是挺快
Well, that was fast.
看来我现在要回去舔拉扎拉了
I guess I have to go crawling back to Lazarra now.
我们预料到了
As we knew you would.
我已经准备好
I've got my checkbook
支票簿和急救箱了
and my first aid kit ready,
就看结果何如了
depending on the outcome.
这是我的地盘
This is my city,
你要吃点苦头才能知道这一点
and you've come to learn that the hard way.
我知道你贿赂了门卫工会的负责人
I know you bribed Mr. Santulli,
圣图里先生
the head of the Door & Custodial Union,
逼他的人继续工作
to get his men back to work.
查克 你的故事很有趣
That's a cute story, Chuck.
但我个人不喜欢小说
But I prefer nonfiction myself.
我们决定维持原来的百分之二
We settled at the original two percent number.
而你又一次证明了
So once again, you've proved yourself
你只是一事无成地浪费了我的时间
to be nothing more than a colossal waste of my time.
但是
Ah, but see,
我录了视频
I have video.
最近怎么样
How you doing?
私人庄园 整个沙滩都是你的
It's a private estate. Full beach access.
圣诞节时的考艾岛可是特别美的
Kauai at Christmastime is pretty special.
那么 你的人什么时候能复工呢
So, when can we get your boys back on the door?
马上就能
Right away.
谢谢你把狗借给我
Thanks for the use of the pooch.
客气了
Sure. Thanks a lot.
一发现你们俩之间的勾当
Once you were spotted together,
我在金融犯罪部门的人顺藤摸瓜
my financial crimes people threw a net
又发现了电汇问题
and found the wire transfers.
你很擅于藏钱 但是
You may be sophisticated at hiding baksheesh, but, uh,
圣图里可没什么经验
Santulli isn't.
你的脸红了
That flush on your face is that, uh,
是因为冲浪 赛马 还是别的什么的
surf, turf or something else?
这些对媒体来说
This would make a real juicy morsel
可是顿大餐啊
to throw to the press.
我想你的对手们
Yeah, I can imagine every outlet
都想来分一杯羹
would want a bite.
但我是个识大体的人
But... I'm a reasonable man.
如果你能说服你的富翁朋友们
If you can get your cohort of fellow billies to agree
给门卫增加百分之五的管理费
to a five-percent management fee increase for the doormen,
我就不用把这件事透露给别人
I don't believe I'll see the need to leak this story.
奥利维亚 在纽约杂志的工作还顺利吗
Olivia, how are things at New York Mag?
有人给我爆料就过的很好
Always good when someone calls with a story.
里面怎么样了
What's the situation in there?
查克现在在里面
Chuck's in there right now.
如果这次他没得到自己想要的结果
If his meeting doesn't go the way he wants it to,
那么他就把一个证据确凿的大头条
he's ready to deliver a cover story to you
送给你
with necessary evidence.
如果查克谈判成功 那就不会有什么头条了
If Chuck wins the meeting, there won't be a story.
这次没有 下次就会有了
This time. But a nice raincheck.
那就希望会谈剑拔弩张一些了
Let's hope the meeting combusts then.
我回车上等了
I'll be waiting in the car.
我凭什么相信你
Why the hell would I trust you?
因为你知道他是怎么做的
Because you know how he operates.
而且我需要你一直支持我
And I'll need you in my corner down the line.
行吧
All right.
我们付
We'll pay.
我会亲自召集他们每个人的
I'll round up everybody myself.
巴德 看起来浪头转弯了
It looks like the tides have turned, Bud.
我们毕竟没法与大海抗衡
We can't fight oceanic forces.
你真应该看看我拿出视频的时候
Oh, you should have seen the crimson shade
老拉扎拉那猪肝一样的脸色了
of old Lazarra's cheeks when I showed him what we had.
为了炫耀这场胜利
I wish I had a swatch of it to repaint my living room
我都想把客厅刷成那个颜色了
as a victory trophy.
他们会付的
They're gonna pay.
我去告诉奥利维亚不用等了
Tell Olivia to move on to her next lead?
不
No.
今晚夜色这么美
It's a beautiful night.
我很想找个人聊聊
I'm feeling like a chat.
你这么做的话
You do that, the billionaires of this city
这个城市之亿万富翁肯定不会放过你
are sure to come after you.
我不会明说
I'd never tell.
但我会启发她该去哪挖线索
But I might tell her where to look.
你的前任们
Former holders of your very office
可都被富翁们打掉了
did not survive that attack.
你确定让我们成为活靶子
Are you sure painting targets on our backs
是明智之举吗
is the best move right now?
我也没什么见不得人的秘密了
No more skeletons in my closets to rattle.
让他们尽管拿放大镜来审查我吧
Let 'em just try and Spitzer me.
你是不想干了吗
Are you looking for your way out of this job?
在我明确告诉你先等等之后 你还疯狂买入
You pigged out on those other sportswear companies dropping
其他下跌的运动服装公司股票
after I explicitly told you to wait.
我料到你会发现的
I knew you'd see it.
我有信心这会有所回报
That's how confident I was that they'd pay off.
也的确如此
And they did.
数据和我的假设一致
The numbers supported my hypothesis.
我把你从分析师提上来
I upped you from analyst
是让你支持我的决定
so you could take positions I supported,
前卫爵士乐萨克斯风手
不是让你像艾瑞克·杜菲独奏一样
not so you could go off and improve on your own
自己另起炉灶
like an Eric Dolphy solo.
好吧 我等过了
Yeah, well, I waited.
然后拉斯科股价开始回升了
And then Rask started rebounding,
所以我就行动了
so I pulled the trigger.
幸亏有我 梅森碳能公司还不知情
And thanks to me, Mase Carb's in the black now.
你不该这么做
You shouldn't have done that.
我说过别这么做了 就算拉斯科股价变化
I already told you no. My last instructions still stood,
我最后的指令依然有效
despite the change in Rask's price.
该赚的钱没赚到 就像是看到一辆甲壳虫车
Leaving money on the table is like seeing
却不打人一样
a punch buggy and not punching someone.
一种游戏 见到甲壳虫车第一时间喊"甲壳虫"并打旁人一下
就是感觉不痛快
It just feels wrong.
但我本可以听你的
But I could have listened to you.
应该
Should.
我本应该听你的
I should have listened to you.
这次我可以给你掩饰过去
I will protect you this time.
普林斯不会知道是你做的决定
Prince won't know you made this call.
但你在玩的这场游戏...
But this game you're playing...
就像麦尔斯乐队的专辑《泼妇酒酿》一样
Yeah. Like Miles's band recording Bitches Brew.
极具革命性和挑衅意味的一张专辑
没有规则
No net.
我明白
I got it.
阿斯特拉运动在得知
Astra Sports has canceled its buyout
拉斯科运动服饰的
of Rask Sportswear
首席执行官小斯图尔特·拉斯科
after learning of CEO Stuart Rask, Jr's
和朝鲜领导人金正恩有秘密关系后
secret partnership with North Korean dictator
取消了对该公司的收购
Kim Jong-un.
老天
Jesus.
这就是你一直压着的事吗
This is what you were sitting on?
斯图伊几年前和丹尼斯·罗德曼
Stuey went to North Korea with Dennis Rodman
一起去了朝鲜 尽管当时其他运动服装公司
some years ago, even after the other sportswear companies
都取消行程 退出不干了
canceled and backed out.
不简单啊 为什么
Remarkable. Why?
拉斯科那时候还是个时装品牌
Rask was still a boutique brand back then.
他们需要扩张
They needed to grow.
旅行归来时他们带回了大量的资金
They came back from their trip fully capitalized.
金正恩一直以来都是秘密合伙人 现在还是
Kim's been a silent partner this whole time. Still is.
可如今...
Until now...
看看后市股价收报机吧
Look at the after-market ticker.
拉斯科要倒闭了
Rask is tanking.
联邦贸易委员会在进行全面调查
Federal Trade Commission's doing a full probe.
瓦格斯宝贝 你行啊
Well, Wagsy, you did it.
你打断了收购 把它扔向了虎狼之口
You killed the buyout and fed it to the dogs.
斯图伊...
Hey, Stu...
这...
It...
听我...
Listen...
我们可以在彩排的时候谈这件事吗
can't we just talk about this at rehearsal?
斯图伊把我踢出乐队了
Stuey just kicked me out of the band.
奥利维亚告诉我拉扎拉的股票
Olivia told me that Lazarra article
今晚会下跌
should drop tonight.
我们最好未雨绸缪
We'd better batten down the hatches.
不用 让暴风雨来得更猛烈些吧 我准备好了
Nah, let the gale blow. I'm ready.
我在尝试像《各怀鬼胎》的哈克曼一样思考
I'm trying to think like Hackman in Heist,
电影中吉恩·哈克曼扮演了一个经验丰富的强盗
想搞清楚为什么让拉扎拉与你为敌
to understand why turning Lazarra against you
是明智之举
is the smart play,
但却想不明白
and I am coming up dry.
这是我父亲很久以前教给我的
Well, something my father taught me long ago.
有时候你就得舍弃一些东西
Sometimes, you just have to break some shit.
搞清楚对手的反应会有多强烈
Find out the strength of the reaction on the other side.
随心而行 不靠智慧
Use your will. Not your wits.
让他们知道你的行动
And make them know your moves
无法预测
can't be anticipated.
没有谁是安全的
That no one is safe.
我可不确定这种老套的伎俩
I'm not sure that old school crap
还行得通
is still gonna play.
美国著名酒馆歌手 钢琴家
老一套的伎俩就像鲍比·肖特的表演
The old school crap plays like Bobby Short.
你只需要知道什么时候用就行了
You just have to know when.
偶尔我酩酊大醉的时候...
Sometime when I'm drunk enough...
S04E07查克讲"吃饼人"的故事 解释为何会成为受虐狂
问问我关于"吃煎饼的人"的事
ask me about pancake eaters.
就能解释清楚了
That'll explain it.
好吧 这样清楚些了
Okay. Well, it better.
你跟我保证了这个季度会大获全胜 查克
You promised me a winning season, Chuck.
可现在我们看起来就像是纽约足球队一样
Right now we're looking like the New York Jets.
在我不得不辞职去25/8区竞选之前
I'm running out of time before I'll have to quit
我的时间不多了
and campaign 25/8.
我从没幻想过你会永远站在我这一边
I am under no illusion that you'll be by my side forever.
但现在
But right now,
我们得到了最大的授权
we've got our biggest mandate on the docket.
我还不能失去我的王牌干将
I can't lose my MVP yet.
我需要你 凯特
I need you, Kate.
我向你保证 而且我猜你甚至也能感觉到
And I commit here, and I sense that you can even feel it
我们马上要大赢一把了
that we are about to have some very big wins.
而且是正义的那种
And the right kind.
为了民众 就像门卫得到五个点的补贴一样
For the folks, like the five percent the doorman got.
这会为你下一步去向助上一臂之力
Ones that will propel you where you want to go.
你的去向也是众望所归
Where we all need you to go.
一旦我们解决了这个案子 做好准备之后
And then, once we're done with that and we're ready,
你会得到我毫无保留的支持
you will have my full-throated endorsement
也可以动用我所有的人脉
and use of all my connections.
好吧 头儿
Okay, Boss.
- 他们要撤销合作了 - 奥运会吗
- They're pulling them. - The games?
国际体育委员会表示...
From the International Commission of Sport...
"鉴于我们的主要赞助商涉嫌
"With the human rights abuses at the hand of
滥用人权...
our main sponsor...
这一做法直接违背了我们的理念...
in direct contravention to the spirit of the...
场馆建设延迟 以及其他的无数问题...
delays in construction and innumerable other problems...
决定重新开始
re-opening a modified
一场有修改的 精简的招投标"
and condensed bid process to be completed."
拉斯科濒临破产
Rask is facing bankruptcy,
斯图伊下个星期也将因为滥用人权的罪名
and Stuey is being hauled in front of Congress next week
送审议会了
on human rights abuses.
他们找了其他赞助商帮忙 但没人出头
They looked to other sponsors, but no one stepped up.
目前局势太不明朗了
Too smoky at the moment.
当发现没法用财政解决
When they saw they couldn't pull it off financially,
他们就开始另寻赞助商了
they started making outgoing calls.
是的
Yes.
我们应该见面谈谈这事
We should meet and talk about it.
我看到你没有解雇利婉
I see you didn't fire Rian.
普林斯生气了吗
Was Prince upset?
我给她打了掩护
I covered for her, actually.
我想她吸取教训了
I saw that she had learned the lesson.
你把功劳归给她还是你自己呢
Did you take the credit for her or for you?
我能得到什么奖励呢
What would I stand to gain?
你的自由
Your freedom.
如果普林斯把你解雇了
If Prince fired you.
不
No.
我想留下
I want to stay.
你看到关于奥运会的新闻了吗
You saw the news about the games?
普林斯不只是在操纵市场
Prince isn't just playing the markets.
他在下一盘很大的棋
His chessboard is much bigger,
而我觉得他还没走完这一步
and I don't think he's done making his moves yet.
当我完成后 这座城市会焕然一新
When I'm done, this city will look very different.
那边 你看到了吗
Over there, you see that?
奥运村就建在那里
That's where the Athletes' Village will go.
等到运动会结束时 我们就把它
We'll turn it all into low-income housing
全部改造为低收入住房
after the games are over.
那边呢
And that there,
我们会建水上运动中心
is where we'll build the aquatic center.
之后会被用作一个公共游泳馆
It can then be used as a public natatorium after.
史上首次纽约奥运会
The very first New York Olympics.
工程量大着呢 迈克
It's a lot of work, Mike.
这座城市衰败了
The city's down,
破败不堪 伤痕累累
busted up, hurting.
这是重建它的绝好机会
It's the perfect opportunity to rebuild.
每当纽约走向消亡时...
Every time New York has fallen...
总会被一个伟人挽救和重建
It has been lifted up and rebuilt by a great man.
这一次就是你了
And that's you this time.
我们
Us.
你不仅会继续做教练
Not only will you keep your coaching job,
你将成为所有攀岩项目的主教练
you'll now be head coach of all sport climbing.
监督所有的三个项目
You'll oversee all three events,
先锋攀岩 速度攀岩
lead climbing, speed climbing,
还有抱石攀岩
and bouldering.
而在你看到我完成建设这里之前
And the version of this place you'll see before I'm done,
你不会想太快离开的
you won't want to leave so quickly.
如果他是我想的那样
If he is who I think he is,
我或许可以重新开始新的工作
I may be able to start doing my job differently,
改变我的目的 进而改变我的为人
to change my purpose and who I am as a result.
你把太多东西押在那篇新闻上了
You've got a lot riding on that read.
你还是觉得我对他的看法有误吗
You still think I'm wrong about him?
我觉得我们都应该小心行事
I think we should both proceed with caution.
我认为应当考虑到 他所做的一切
I think it's worth considering that what he did
或许不是基于一些冠冕堂皇的
might not have been based on some
道义上的原因
lofty ethical reason.
如果不是道义 那是什么呢
What then, if not ethics?
他老婆昨天来过了
His wife came by yesterday.
我知道他结婚了
I knew he was married,
但他老婆好像出局了
but that she's out of the picture.
没错 但她还是来这里了
Yeah. But she still showed up here.
这一切都是某种展现浪漫的方式吗
All of this is some big romantic gesture?
要么是这个 要么他有自恋型人格障碍
That, or he has Narcissistic Personality Disorder.
这是什么意思 就普林斯而言
And what would that mean, in Prince's case?
他认为他比任何人都强
He thinks he's better than everyone else.
而在他得到他想要的之前 他不会罢手
And he won't stop till he gets what he wants.
给你的 萨尔特教练
For you, Coach Salter.
纽约2028
真不错
Nice.
你知道现在下定论还为时尚早吗
You know this is far from a sure thing?
当然 还有很多事需要做
Sure, there's a lot left to do.
我得取得一些支持
I'll have to gather some support.
一些支持吗 你需要一个联盟
Some support? You'll need a coalition.
你得改变立法
You have to move the legislature.
推动整个政治机构 城市和大州
The whole political machine, city and state.
还有群众
And the people too.
得把实现这一想法的决心推销出去
Need to sell the goddamned commission on the idea.
当然 这一切我都准备好了
Sure. I'm ready for all of that.
还有其他的事
There's something else.
我还没打算放弃
I'm not ready to give up.
关于我们俩
On us.
还生我的气吗
Still mad at me?
我保有这个权力
I reserve the right.
穿上夹克试试嘛 看看你喜不喜欢
Try on the jacket. See if you like it.
一旦正式宣布
I'll put it on
纽约是承办城市 我立马穿上它
as soon as New York is officially announced.
而在那之前我是不会搬过来的
And I'm not moving here until then.
好吧 但如果我是你的话 我会开始看公寓了
All right. But if I were you, I'd start looking at apartments.
一起吃晚饭吗
Dinner?
行啊
Sure.
吃晚饭
Dinner.
♪你无法藏匿♪
You can't hide
♪你说谎的眼神♪
Your lyin' eyes
♪而你的微笑♪
And your smile
♪是失败的伪装♪
Is a thin disguise
■
更多精彩 请登录深影论坛 shinybbs.vip
深影字幕组微博 weibo.com/syfansub
♪我想现在♪
I thought by now
♪你该意识到了♪
You'd realize
♪你无法藏匿♪
There ain't no way to hide
♪你说谎的眼神♪
Your lyin' eyes
■
关注深影字幕组
微信公众号，更
多影视资讯，等
你来发现
♪你无法藏匿♪
There ain't no way to hide
♪你说谎的眼神♪
Your lyin' eyes